[{"question":"# Q1. When you create a new, blank presentation, you begin with one blank slide. What is the layout name of this slide?","options":["Blank","Title slide","Title and Content","Title Onty"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Title slide"},{"question":"# Q2. What do you use to align objects on a slide to one another?","options":["Layout tools","Arrange tools","Design Ideas feature","Picture tools","      `In MS PP 2019 it's called \"Drawing Tools\". There is no such answer but there is a function called \"Arrange\""],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Arrange tools"},{"question":"# Q3. Which option must be enabled if you want to manipulate the playback of a video file during a presentation?","options":["Record Side Show","Use Presenter View","Show Playback Controls","Show Media Controls"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Show Media Controls"},{"question":"# Q4. Which feature analyzes the content of your slides and offers suggested options?","options":["Design ideas","Smartart","Browse for Themes","Add-Ins"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Design ideas"},{"question":"# Q5. Where can you configure advanced PDF options?","options":["the Options tab","the Home tab","the Print dialog box","the Share tab","      `Should be in the printer window not in the options menu"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"the Print dialog box"},{"question":"# Q6. Which tab is best for adding various types of objects to slides?","options":["Animations","view","File","Insert"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Insert"},{"question":"# Q7. Which SmartArt category can you use to make informational graphics out of bullet points?","options":["all of these answers","Pyramid","List","Matrix"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"all of these answers"},{"question":"# Q8. What is NOT checked when you run the Accessibility Checker?","options":["reading order","slide titles","missing alt text","grammar","      [Source](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/office/rules-for-the-accessibility-checker-651e08f2-0fc3-4e10-aaca-74b4a67101c1?ns=powerpnt&version=16&ui=en-us&rs=en-us&ad=us)"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"grammar"},{"question":"# Q9. How can you change the appearance of a table in one click?","options":["Apply a cell stye.","Apply a graphic style.","Apply a table style.","Right-click a table and choose a new style.","Table Tools -> Design Tab -> Table Styles"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Apply a table style."},{"question":"# Q10. Which option changes a text box so that it automatically changes shape to fit longer text?","options":["Resize shape to fit text","Do not autofit","none of these answers","Shrink text on overflow"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Resize shape to fit text"},{"question":"# Q11. Which three shadow properties can be adjusted in PowerPoint?\n\n```\nA. Focal Point\nB. Depth\nC. Blur\nD. Angle\nE. Distance\n\n```","options":["A, B, C","A, C, E","B, C, D","C, D, E"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"C, D, E"},{"question":"# Q12. You want your presentation to play continuously on screen, What option must you set?","options":["Use Presenter view","Advance slides manually","Advance slides automatically","Loop continuously until 'Esc'","      `Slide Show Tab -> Set Up Slide Show -> Show options -> Loop continuously until 'Esc'"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Loop continuously until 'Esc'"},{"question":"# Q13. Which statement about the Compress Pictures command is true?","options":["You can compress all images at the same time.","You cannot delete cropped areas.","There are no options for print output.","You can compress only one image at a time."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"You can compress all images at the same time."},{"question":"# Q14. You have a Word document you would like to import as an outline into a PowerPoint presentation. How should you format the text in your Word document that you want to be the slide content?\n\n- [x] Heading Style 2\n- [ ] Subtitle\n- [ ] Content Style\n- [ ] List 2\n\n```\nHighlight the content you want to use as a slide title, and select Heading 1 in Styles.\nHighlight the content you want to use as the slide text, and select Heading 2 in Styles.\nIf your Word document contains no Heading 1 or Heading 2 styles, PowerPoint will create a slide for each paragraph in your content.\n\n```","options":[]},{"question":"# Q15. In what manner can you filter comments?","options":["by length","by author","by date","by urgency"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"by author"},{"question":"# Q16. Which Arrow Options choice will hide the mouse cursor when presenting, except when the cursor is moved?\n\n- [x] Automatic\n- [ ] Hidden\n- [ ] none of these answers\n- [ ] Visible\n\n```\nIf hidden is selected the courser stays hidden no matter what.\n\n```","options":[]},{"question":"# Q17. Which chart type is best suited for displaying annual financial data for a 10-year period?","options":["donut chart","line or area chart","area chart","pie chart"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"line or area chart"},{"question":"# Q18. If you want to create an organizational chart, which SmartArt category works best?","options":["Pyramid","Relationship","Hierarchy","Matrix"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Hierarchy"},{"question":"# Q19. When printing multiple handouts, which option will group multipage documents together and make them easier to distribute?","options":["Print on Both Sides","Uncollated","Print One-sided","Collated"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Collated"},{"question":"# Q20. How can you adjust which data in a table is used when working on a chart?","options":["Click the Switch Row/Column button.","Click the Refresh Data button.","Click the Select Data button.","Click the Edit Data button."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Click the Select Data button."},{"question":"# Q21. Which view lets you see additional information on a second monitor when delivering a presentation?","options":["Normal view","Reading view","Slide Sorter view","Presenter view"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Presenter view"},{"question":"# Q22. A picture looks good in your slide show but pixelated when you print it. How can you fix this?\n\n- [ ] Compress the picture and use the Print (220 ppi) resolution setting.\n- [ ] Select Best scale for slide show, increase the picture resolution and resize the picture to the original size\n- [x] Remove picture compression.\n- [ ] Change the printer property settings to print in a higher resolution.\n\n```Personal Hint:\nFile Tab -> Options -> Advanced -> Image Size and Quality -> Do not compress images in file\nFile Tab -> Options -> Advanced -> Print -> High quality\n\n```","options":[]},{"question":"# Q23. You have inserted s video on a slide and want the video to automaaticlly start 2 seconods after the associated slide appears. How can you accomplish this?","options":["Use playback timings.","Use animation timings.","Use animation triggers.","Use video timings."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Use animation timings."},{"question":"# Q24. When inserting pictures, how can you avoid distorting the pictureif it is resized later?","options":["Use best scale for slide show.","Lock the aspect ratio.","Compress the picture.","Set the picture to be relative to the orignal picture size."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Lock the aspect ratio."},{"question":"# Q25. Which Protect Presentation option protects a presentation from accidental changes?","options":["Always Open Read-Only","Add a Digital Signature","Encrypt with Password","Mark as Final"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Always Open Read-Only"},{"question":"# Q26. How can you change colors in your presentation all at once without changing the design?","options":["Apply a Color Template.","Apply a Color Theme.","Apply a Color Palette.","Customize the Color Fills."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Apply a Color Theme."},{"question":"# Q27. What function allows you to borrow slides from a presentation fro an other presentation?","options":["Borrow Slides","There is no special fuction. You must use Copy and Pase","Reuse Slides","Find Slides"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Reuse Slides"},{"question":"# Q28. What is the term used for the arrangement of elements on a slide, such as Title and Content?","options":["theme","design","sheme","layout"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"layout"},{"question":"# Q29. How would you change a list of text to a visual diagram on a slide?","options":["Convert to WordArt.","Convert to Shapes.","Convert to SmartArt.","Convert to Picture."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Convert to SmartArt."},{"question":"# Q30. You need to reorder the levels of shapes on a SmartArt diagram. How can this be done","options":["Retype the text","Change the shapes from rifht to left.","Promote Shapes and/or Demote Shapes.","Move the shapes up and down."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Promote Shapes and/or Demote Shapes."},{"question":"# Q31. Why would you trim a video?","options":["To crop the video thumbnail.","To resize the video.","To remove background noise in the video.","To remove some of the beginning and/or end of the video."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"To remove some of the beginning and/or end of the video."},{"question":"# Q32. How would you save your layouts, colors, fonts, effects, background styles and content for others to use with their presentations?\n\n- [x] Export the file as a template.\n- [ ] Save the file as a PDF.\n- [ ] Save the file as a POTX.\n- [ ] Save the file as a PPTX.\n\n```\nPersonal Hint: There are multiple file suffixes for templates (.potx, .potm, .pot).\n\n```","options":[]},{"question":"# Q33. You are creating an industrial presentation of a new software program and would like to include an image of your program. How can you use PowerPoint to do this?","options":["Use the Copy command.","Use the Screenshot command. (Office2019)","Use the Print key.","Use the Capture Screen command."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Use the Screenshot command. (Office2019)"},{"question":"# Q34. How can you add more layouts to the Layout Gallery?","options":["Customize the Layout Gallery.","Add Slide Layouts to the Slide Master.","Use the Add Layouts command.","Use the Insert Layouts command."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Add Slide Layouts to the Slide Master."},{"question":"# Q35. Why would you use the Outline view?","options":["To see only the text in placeholders.","To present the slides at a high level.","To add text from a Word document.","To organize your slides."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"To see only the text in placeholders."},{"question":"# Q36. The text on the left and right of the slide are cut off in print preview. How can you fix this in the printer settings?","options":["Unselect High Quality.","Select Scale to Fit Paper.","Select Frame Slides.","Select Frame Slides."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Select Scale to Fit Paper."},{"question":"# Q37. In addition to organizing your slides, how else can sections increase your productivity?","options":["In addition to organizing your slides, how else can sections increase your productivity?.","All the slides in a section can be selected at once to apply changes such as transitions, layouts or hiding slides.","Sections can be exported as a separate presentation.","You can resize all the slides in a section at once."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"All the slides in a section can be selected at once to apply changes such as transitions, layouts or hiding slides."},{"question":"# Q38. You have many slides that you need to reorder. How would you accomplish this?","options":["Move the slides in Slide Show view.","Renumber the slides in Outline view.","Move the slides in the Slide Sorter view.","Reset the slide footers."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Move the slides in the Slide Sorter view."},{"question":"# Q39. What can be seen in Presenter view?","options":["Timer.","Notes.","Side Navigator.","all of these answers."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"all of these answers."},{"question":"# Q40. How can you format the entire contents of a text box?","options":["Click the dashed/dotted border of the text box.","Right-click the text box and select Select All.","Click the Fond button on the Home tab.","Double-click any word in the text box."]},{"question":"# Q41. You have a large number of objects on your slide. How can you use the selection pane to help you identify the objects quickly?","options":["Select the show/hide icons next to the objects.","Rename the objects with meaningful names.","Drag and drop the objects.","Tab through the objects and note each object as it's highlighted."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Rename the objects with meaningful names."}]